잘 왔어
Thanks for coming by.
결혼식 때문에 몇 가지
의논할 게 있었거든
We wanted to bounce some ideas off
of you about the wedding ceremony.
- 왜 그래? 괜찮아?
- 아니 그냥...
-What's the matter? Are you okay?
-It's just...
Monica said "wedding."
모니카가 '결혼'이라고 했잖아
둘 중 하나가 축사같은 걸
읽었음 해서
We thought one of you
could read something.
그래, 그것도 하지 뭐
Okay, yeah, I guess I can do that too.
그것도?
Too?
다른 걸 계획하고
있는 게 있었거든
I kind of have something else
planned for you guys.
- 뭔지 얘기해 주면 안 돼?
- 미안해
-Do you mind telling us what it is?
-Sorry.
이건 비밀로 하고 싶어
I'm kind of keeping this one
on the QT.
그게 뭐던 간에
윙크와 관계있길 바래
Whatever it is,
I hope it involves winking.
- 다 있었네
- 어서 와
-Hey.
생날작가와 통화했는데...
I talked to one of the DOOL writers..
- 생날이 뭐야?
- 생의 나날들
-What is DOOL?
-Days Of Our Lives.
내가 맡은 인물이
혼수상태에서 깨어난대!
You won't believe it. My character
is coming out of his coma!
- 잘 됐다
- 좋겠다, 조이
-That's wonderful.
-Wow, Joey.
그 뿐만 아니라
새 뇌도 갖게 된대
And not only that.
I'm getting a new brain!
일뿐만 아니라
개인적으로도 경사네
So great things are happening at work
and in your personal life.
새 뇌를 갖는다고?
You're getting a new brain?
출연자 한 사람을
죽게 하고
They're killing off
one of the characters...
그 여자 뇌를 내 몸에
이식하는 거야
and her brain is being transplanted
into my body.
뭐? 뇌 이식이라고?
What? A brain transplant?
말도 안 된다
It's ridiculous.
석 달 반이나 섹스 못 한
네가 말이 안 되지
It's ridiculous that you
haven't had sex in three months.
겨울이라 길에
사람이 별로 없단 말야
It's winter.
There are fewer people on the street.
누굴 죽이는데?
Who are they killing off?
세실리아 먼로라고
제시카 락하트 역 맡은 배우
Cecilia Monroe.
She plays Jessica Lockhart.
안 돼!
No!
그 여자 사람 얼굴에
물 뿌리는 거 정말 잘 하지
She is so good at throwing drinks
in people's faces.
한 번도 음료수 끝까지
마시는 걸 못 봤어
I don't think I've ever seen
her finish a drink.
뺨 때리는 건 어떻고?
나도 한 번 해보고 싶다
The way she slaps people.
Wouldn't you love to?
하지 마
Don't do it.
꽤 오래 출연했잖아
And she's been on the show forever.
그 여자 역 하기
정말 만만치 않을 거야
It's gonna be really hard
to fill her shoes.
Help me out here.
한 가지 물어보자
When you come out
of the brain transplant...
네가 뇌 이식 수술을
마치게 되면
you are going to be her?
그 여자가 된다고?
그래, 몸은 그대로
드레이크 라모레고
Yes, but in Drake Ramoray's body.
뭐가 이해가 안 되는 거야?
너 과학자잖아
Why is this so hard for you to get?
I thought you were a scientist.
The One With Joey's New Brain
The One Where Joey Gets A New Brain
레이첼, 저기 저 남자
Rach, so that guy there:
게이일까, 아닐까?
Straight or gay?
저렇게 매력있으면
당근 게이지
Oh, yeah, he's too cute
to be straight.
저 가슴 큰 여자가
도와줄 거야
Knockers will help us
figure it out.
좋아, 게이 아니네
All right, straight.
노골적이기도 하고
And not subtle.
핸드폰 놓고 갔어
He left his cell phone.
건터한테 분실물함에
넣어두라고 해야겠네
We could have Gunther
put it in lost and found.
아님 저걸로 중국에 전화해서
그쪽 사람들 안부나 묻던가
Or we could use it to call China,
see how those guys are doing.
그 사람이 자기 전화로
전화를 걸었는데
What if he calls his own cell phone
and I answer...
내가 전화받아서
둘이 사랑에 빠진다면?
and we start talking
and we fell in love?
멋진 이야기 아니니?
Would that be a great story?
디지털 시대의
동화같잖아
Kind of like a fairy tale
for the digital age.
정말 괜찮은 얘긴데
저 전화 내가 가져야지
That does sound great.
I'm getting the phone.
뭐? 잠깐
네가 왜 가져?
What? Wait.
Why do you get the story?
나 데이트 해 본지
오래됐잖아
I haven't been
out on a date in so long.
피비, 너 3일 전에도
데이트했잖아
Phoebe, you had a date three days ago.
그건 데이트가 아니라 그냥
두 친구가 잠자리 같이 한 거야
That wasn't a date. That was friends
getting together and having sex.
좋아, 전화기 내가 가질래
Okay. Great. I get the phone.
안 돼, 태그하고
일주일 전에 헤어졌으면서
No way. You just broke up with Tag
a week ago.
그리고 지금껏 누군가를 다시
사랑할 수 없을거라 생각했지
Yeah, and until now, I didn't think
I would love again.
- 속을 줄 알고?
- 잠깐
-Nice try.
-Wait.
어떻게 하면 공평하게
결정할 수 있지?
How do we fairly decide
who gets the phone?
I don't know.
몰라
어쩌면...
Maybe we could...
아하! 느림보!
Ah-ha! Too slow!
아하! 잘난 체하긴
Ah-ha! Too cocky.
'실버컵 스튜디오'
엄마가 뭐라시든
그 사람 만날 거예요
I'm dating him.
There's nothing you can do.
절대 못 만나
Yes, there is.
Are you going to kill him
like you did Charles?
어쩌실 건데요? 찰스처럼
죽이기라도 하시게요?
오, 얘야
Oh, my baby.
컷!
Cut!
정말 대단했어요, 뺨 때리는 거
실감나던데 어떻게 하셨죠?
That was great. And that slap looked
so real. How do you do that?
- 수년간의 경험 덕분이지
- 얼음 좀 주세요
-Oh, just years of experience.
-Can I get some ice here?!
정말 훌륭하시다는
말씀을 드리고 싶네요
I just wanted to say how wonderful
I think you are.
댁이 죽어간다는
그 팬은 아니죠?
You're not the fan who's dying,
are you?
조이 트리비아니입니다
어제 같이 촬영했죠
I'm Joey Tribbiani.
We did a scene together yesterday.
- 혼수상태에 빠진 남자요
- 그게 진짜 사람이었어요?
-I'm the guy in the coma.
-Oh, that was a real person?
선배님 그만두실 때
제가 뇌를 받게 되었으니
Since I'm getting your brain
when you leave the show...
혹시 조언이라도...
I was wondering if..
- 내가 그만둔다고?
- 왜요? 무슨 말 들으셨어요?
-I'm leaving the show?
-Why? Did you hear something?
누가 그러던가요?
Who told you that?
- 작가중 한 사람이
- 누구? 대머리 아님 꺽다리?
-One of the writers.
-Was it bald or was it tall?
사실이 아니니
중요한 게 아니지
You know, it doesn't matter,
because it is not true.
그럼요
Okay.
사실이라고 해도 어떻게 감히
내 조언을 듣겠다는 거지?
And if it were true, how dare you come
to me and ask me for tips...
내가 20년이나
해 온 역할인데!
about a character I've played
for 20 years!
선배님...
잘 하시네요
Miss Monroe..
Oh, there you go.
Okay, look, I have an idea.
좋아, 생각이 있어
Why don't we see what kind of numbers
he has on his speed dial...
단축 다이얼에
무슨 번호가 있나 봐서
그 사람과 공통점이
더 많은 쪽이 갖는 걸로 하자
and then whoever has more in common
with him gets the phone.
- 좋아
- 그래
-Fine. All right.
-All right.
첫 번째는 '엄마'
First name on the speed dial is "Mom."
우리 엄만 자살하셨는데
Oh. I lost my mom to suicide.
안 돼, 마지막 블루베리 머핀
먹을 때 그거 써먹었잖아
You can't use that to get the cute guy
and the last blueberry muffin.
오늘 벌써 써먹었니?
미안해
Did I use that already today? Sorry.
'벤, 칼로스, 데이빗...'
"Ben, Carlos, David.."
Oh, I win. He's got Barney's
on his speed dial.
야! 내가 이겼다
바니스가 단축 다이얼에 있어
You don't know it's Barney's
the store.
그게 바니스 백화점인지
어떻게 알아?
That could be his friend's
house, a bar..
친구 집이나 술집일 수도 있고
Who has Barney's the store
on their speed dial?
누가 백화점 번호를
단축 다이얼에 넣니?
His new girlfriend.
그 사람 새 여자친구
What is that?
무슨 소리지?
I think it's the Dying Cat Parade.
고양이 비명소리 같은데
Sounds like it's coming
from across the street.
길 건너에서
들리는 소리 같은데
-Oh, my God.
-What?
- 맙소사
- 왜?
The thing that Ross was gonna
do at our wedding?
로스가 결혼식 때
한다던 거 있잖아
He was hanging out with me and said,
"You're half Scottish, right?"
어제 나한테 그러더라고
'너 반은 스코트랜드계지'?
그럴 리가 없어
오빠는 아닐 거야
No. There is no way.
It cannot be Ross.
돌아가시겠네
자긴 왜 스코트랜드계야?
Unbelievable.
Why is your family Scottish?
자기 오빤 왜 로스야?
Why is your family Ross?
절대 연주하게 하면 안 돼
다 집에 가 버릴걸
He cannot play at our wedding.
들어 봐, 저건 소음이야!
I mean, come on. That is just noise!
노래도 아니라고
It's not even a song.
잠깐, 잘 들어보면
Wait. If you listen very carefully...
쿨 앤 더 갱의
'셀리브레이션' 같은데
I think it's "Celebration"
by Kool and the Gang.
그쪽 말이 맞았어요
날 없애기로 했대요
You're right.
They are writing me out of the show.
언제인진 모르지만
아마 곧 그럴 거예요
They don't know exactly when
it's going to happen, but soon...
그럼 그걸로 끝이죠
and then that's it.
미안해요, 나였다면
절대로 빼지 않았을 거예요
If it was up to me,
you would never leave the show.
- 고마워요
- 정말이에요
-Yeah, thanks.
-I mean it.
어떻게 선배님과
팬들한테 이럴 수가 있죠?
I can't believe they'd do this to you.
And to your fans.
실망이 대단할 거예요
선배님을 사랑하니까요
They're gonna be devastated.
Heartbroken. They love you so much.
그러게요
Oh, you're right.
고마워요
Thank you.
이름이 뭐랬죠?
What's your name again?
- 조이요
- 고마워요
-Joey.
-Thank you.
말만이라도 고맙네
That is so sweet.
선배님을 찾아 온 이유는
The only reason
I came up to you before...
is because, well...
사실 선배님 역을 한다는 게
너무 긴장돼요
I'm really nervous about being you.
인물의 특징을 잡을 수 있게
도와주실 수만 있다면
If you could help me capture
the essence of the character...
제시카를 살아있도록
도와주세요
Help me keep Jessica alive.
Please?
좋아요, 도와주죠
Joey, I will help you.
이 엉터리 드라마에
애정이 있어서가 아니라
Not because I owe it
to this stupid show...
제시카 때문이죠
but because I owe it to Jessica.
- 그럼요, 정말 고마워요
- 별 소릴
-Oh, thank you so much.
-You're so welcome.
녹화 테이프를 봤거든요
이건 어때요?
I've been watching some tapes.
How's this?
제시카 락하트는 절대
이곳에 다시 오지 않아!
Jessica Lockhart will never
step foot in this place again!
절대로!
Never!
제시카는 영국 억양
쓰지 않는데
Jessica doesn't have
an English accent.
제가 영국 억양 썼어요?
I can do an English accent?
그것도 이력서에
써야겠어요
That baby's going on my resume.
- 안녕, 피비?
- 어서 와
-Hi. How are you?
-Good.
아까 커피숍에서
얘기하다가
Remember when we were
in the coffeehouse...
내가 그 남자 휴대폰
갖기로 한 거 기억나?
we decided I was gonna keep
the cute guy's phone?
전화오면 바로 받으려고
내 핸드백에 넣었잖아?
I was gonna keep it in my purse, so if
it rang, I could just pick it up?
너 내 핸드백에서
핸드폰 훔쳐간 거 기억해?
Do you remember going into my purse
and stealing the phone?
그건 모르겠는데
Ooh, now you lost me.
- 네가 훔쳤잖아
- 안 훔쳤어
-You stole the phone.
-No, I didn't.
그럼 내가 전화해도
벨이 안 울리겠네?
You're saying if I called it,
it wouldn't ring?
- 당연하지
- 좋아
-No.
-Okay.
그 전에 새로 산
벨소리 나는 핸드백 보여줄게
But while you dial, let me show you
the features of my new ringing handbag.
와, 진짜 된다
Oh, it does work.
- 피비
- 이건 다른 전화야
-Phoebe.
-That is a different phone.
그래? 여보세요, 네
레이첼 있어요?
Oh, is it? Hello. Yes, hi.
Is Rachel there?
네, 있어요, 잠깐만요
나한테 온 거잖아
Yes, she is. Just one moment, please.
It's for me!
확실한 증거네
That is damning evidence.
어머나, 그 남자일 거야
Oh, my God. I bet that's him.
디지털 동화가
막 시작되고 있어
My digital fairy tale's
about to begin.
네, 레이첼...
Would you stop doing that?
그거 좀 그만 할래?
Hello? Yes, I'm the one
who found your phone.
여보세요? 제가 그쪽
전화 주운 사람인데요
-Phoebe, you can't..
-Shh, I'm on a call.
- 피비, 그러면...
- 전화 받는 중이잖아
오늘 저녁에 찾아가세요
8시 30분쯤
Yeah, you can pick it up tonight.
Say, 8:30?
제 아파트에서요
At my apartment.
It's 5 Morton Street,
apartment 14.
모튼 가 5번지 14호예요
그리고 저녁이나
같이 하던가요
And then maybe, you know, after,
we can grab a bite to eat or whatever.
좋아요, 그때 뵙죠, 그럼
Okay. Okay, I'll see you then. Bye.
I will be here when he comes over.
그 사람 올 때
나도 올 거란 거 알겠지
몇 시에 오는 줄 알고?
How will you know what time
to come over?
네가 말했잖아
You just said it.
Oh.
인물의 특징은
자신감에서 나와요
The essence of the character
is rooted in her confidence.
So when Jessica enters a room,
for instance...
제시카가
방에 들어서면 즉시
she owns everything...
모든 게 그녀의 것이죠
and every person in that room.
그 방의 사람들도
- 해 봐요
- 좋아요
-You try it.
-Okay.
방에 화난 게 아니죠
He's not mad at the room.
다시 해 봐요, 소유했어요
방을 소유했다고요
Try it again. He owns it.
He owns the room.
벌써 자기 거라고요
방을 소유했다니까요
It is his. He owns, owns,
owns the room! He owns it!
좀 이상하지만
나아졌네요
It's a little weird,
but it's getting better.
정말 이 역이 그리울 거예요
앞으론 뭘 하죠?
I'm gonna miss this woman so much.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
20년 동안 해 온건데
It's been 20 years of my life.
잘 된 걸지도 몰라요
Hey, hey. Maybe this is a good thing.
다양한 역을 할 기회를
가질 수 있잖아요
It'll give you a chance to shake
things up. Play different characters.
워낙 재능이 뛰어나시니까
You're so talented.
옛날에 출연제의가 쏟아질 때
떠났어야 했는데
Probably should've just left years ago
when the offers were pouring in...
여기가 너무 편했거든요
but I just got
so comfy here and...
많은 기회를 놓쳤죠
I turned down some amazing work.
예를 들면요?
Like what?
이렇게만 말해두죠
내가 15년 전에만 떠났으면
Well, let's just say
if I'd left 15 years ago...
멕시코 영화계의
판도가 바뀌었을 거라고요
the landscape of Mexican
cinema would be very different today.
와
Wow.
그렇지만
이젠 나도 한물갔어요
But, well, now...
Now's a different time for me.
선배님, 울지 말아요
Oh, hey, come on. Don't do this.
제 말 들어보세요
Let me tell you something, okay?
전 선배님을 뵐 때마다
대단한 배우라고 생각해요
When I watch you do a scene, I'm
thinking, "She is a great actress."
매력적이기도 하고요
But I'm also thinking, "She is hot."
매력적이라고요?
You think I'm hot?
분위기를 압도하잖아요
You own the room.
계속 하던 거나...
We should probably get the...
그래요, 맞아요
Oh, yeah. Yeah, we should get..
제시카가 키스할 때는
So when Jessica kisses a man...
항상
she usually puts...
양손으로 얼굴을 감싸쥐어요
both her hands on the man's face.
저도 봤어요
너무 열정적이라 그런가요?
I notice that.
Is that because she's so passionate?
아뇨, 그래야 카메라에
자기 얼굴만 잡히니까요
No, it's because that way
the camera only sees her.
한 번 해볼래요?
You want to try it?
네, 좋아요
Yeah, okay.
잘 했어요, 아주 잘 했어요
That was good. That was really good.
손 위치가 좀 잘못됐네요
여기 이렇게...
But I think that maybe your hands
are just a little off. They should..
우리 뭐 좀 먹을까?
Well, I feel like a snack.
쇼트브레드 먹을래?
스코트랜드 과자잖아
Do you want some shortbread?
It's Scottish, like you are.
됐어, 난 스코트랜드와
관련된 건 다 싫거든
Oh, no, thanks. I don't like anything
from my Scottish heritage.
뭐라고?
What?
우리 가족은 스코트랜드에서
도망쳐 나왔거든
Well, it's just that my entire family
was run out of Scotland by...
바이킹 때문에
Vikings.
그럼 스코트랜드인의 뿌리를
다시 찾아야 될 것 같네
It sounds like your family's ready
to rediscover its Scottish roots.
결혼식 때 백파이프
연주하지 마
You can't play bagpipes
at the wedding!
어떻게 알았어?
How did you know?
-We heard you play from our apartment.
-Were you the ones who called the cops?
- 아파트에서 나는 소리 들었어
- 경찰에 신고한 게 너였어?
그게 지금
중요한 게 아니잖아
That's not really important right now.
마음은 정말 고마운데
What is important is, while we
appreciate the gesture...
결혼식에 백파이프 연주는
안 어울릴 것 같아
we just don't feel that bagpipes
are appropriate for our wedding.
- 왜?
- 우리가 싫어하니까
-Why not?
-Because we hate them.
내가 연주하는 거 듣고
그 다음에 결정해
Just give me a chance to perform for
you, then decide whatever you want.
무슨 노래 연주할 건지도
비밀이야
I'm not gonna tell you what song
I'm gonna play, either.
그렇지만 연주가 끝나면
Let's just say when it's over...
'셀리브레이션' 무드가
된다는 것만 말해두지
I'll bet there'll be
a wee bit o'celebration.
뭐하는 거야!
Hey, hey!
누구세요?
Who is it?
탐이라고
전화 가지러 왔습니다
It's Tom.
I'm here to pick up the phone.
왜 네가 문열어 주는 거야?
Why do you get to answer the door?
- 안될 건 뭐 있어?
- 여긴 내 아파트야
-Why shouldn't I?
-Because it's my apartment.
그럼 전화기는
내가 줄 거야
Then I get to give him the phone.
좋아, 중국에 전화한 거
잘 설명해 봐
Okay. Good luck explaining
all the calls to China.
안녕하세요
Hi.
우리가 그렇게 오래 싸웠나?
Wow, how long were we arguing for?
전화기 두고 가신 분이
아니네요
You're not the man who left the phone.
- 그 친군 제 비섭니다
- 그 분도 와요?
-No, that's my assistant.
-Is he coming?
아뇨
No.
- 잠시 실례해도 될까요?
- 그럼요
-Could you give us one second?
-Sure.
잠깐만 기다려주세요
We'll be right back, sir.
- 어떡하지?
- 나도 몰라
-What do we do?
-I don't know.
이런 일도 있니?
Can you believe this?
멋진 남자를 기다리는데
더 멋진 남자가 나타나다니
We were waiting for a hot guy
and a hotter one shows up.
그러게
I know..
What?
뭐라고?
Rachel, listen...
레이첼, 있잖아
저 남자 양보하면
if you let me have him,
then I will really owe you one.
이 은혜 안 잊을께
알았어
All right.
너한테 양보하는 대신
All right, I will let you have him.
너 나한테 큰 빚진 거다
But you owe me. You owe me big.
어느 숙녀분께서
저와 저녁을 하실 거죠?
Which one of you will I
take to dinner?
아, 저예요
Oh, that'd be me, sir.
- 먼저 가시죠
- 고마워요
죽인다
Nice.
이 방은 조이가
소유했네요
Well, you certainly own that room.
사실 세 든 거예요
아, 뭔 소린지 이제 알았어요
Actually, I rent the whole place.
I just got what you meant. Thank you.
- 안녕
- 왔어
-Hi.
-Hey.
어머나
Oh, my God.
제시카 락하트가
내 아파트에 있다니
Oh, Jessica Lockhart!
In my apartment!
저 너무 좋아하거든요
너무 너무 좋아해요
I am such a huge fan.
고맙군요...
It's nice to know..
모니카!
Monica!
제 룸메이트, 레이첼이에요
That's my roommate, Rachel.
그래서 여자 속옷이 있었구나
That explains the women's underwear.
그럼요
Sure.
어머나, 정말이네
Oh, my God, it's true!
한 가지 부탁해도 될까요?
Can I just ask you to do me
just one favor?
Certainly.
그럼요
제 뺨 한 대
쳐 주시겠어요?
Would you slap me
right here in the face?
I'd love to, but my lawyer said
I can't do that anymore.
그러고 싶지만 변호사가
그러면 안 된대요
자, 어서 가 봐
All right, here we go.
잠깐, 한 가지만 더요
No, wait. Just one moment.
- 당신은 못된 여자야
- 그래도 못 때려요
-You're a stupid bitch.
-I really can't slap you.
- 정말 멋있어요
- 들러줘서 고마워
-My God, you're great.
-Thanks for stopping by.
- 정말 미안해요
- 괜찮아
-I am so sorry about that.
-Oh, no.
사랑받는 덴 익숙하니까
걱정 말아요
Being adored, I'm used to it.
Don't worry about it.
- 와
- 왜?
-Oh, my God.
-What?
대본을 보냈네요
한 번도 보낸 적 없는데
They sent me today's script.
They never send me the script.
- 안 보내요?
- 혼수상태였잖아요
-They don't?
-I'm in a coma.
그럼 나도 대사가 있단 얘긴데
This must mean I have lines.
Oh.
How does it happen?
나 어떻게 죽어요?
You get thrown from a horse
into an electric fence.
말을 타고 가다가
전기 철조망에 떨어지네요
A what? Jessica hates horses.
뭐라고요?
제시카는 말을 싫어하는데
After this she's not gonna be crazy
about electricity, either.
앞으론 전기도
좋아하지 않을 것 같네요
엄마 말 안장 풀어놓은 거
너무 잘했어, 프레드릭
Loosening the saddle on Mother's horse
was brilliant, Fredrick.
전기 철조망도 그렇고
And the electric fence, inspired.
고마워, 자기
Thank you, sweetheart.
엄마가 없다니
믿어지지가 않아
I can't believe she's really gone.
둘러봐, 다 우리 거야
Look around you. All of this is ours.
천만에
I don't think so.
누구세요?
Who are you?
왜 그러니, 디나?
What's the matter, Dina?
네 엄마도
Don't you recognize your own...
못 알아보겠니?
mother?
컷! 잘 했어요
고마워요
Cut! That was great, everybody.
Thank you.
정말 잘 했어요!
That was so wonderful!
나보다 훨씬
잘한 것 같아요
I think that you're a better
Jessica than I ever was.
- 그럴 리가 없죠
- 그렇죠, 그래도 잘했어요
-Oh, no.
-Of course not, but you were good.
고마워요
Thanks.
나 일하게 됐어요
Good news. I got another job.
잘 됐네요, 무슨 일이죠?
Great. Hey, all right! What is it?
과달라하라에서 영화찍어요
A film in Guadalajara.
공항 말이에요?
The airport?
거긴 라과디아고
No, that's LaGuardia.
- 멕시코에 있어요
- 와
-This is Mexico.
-Oh, wow.
얼마나 가 있을 거죠?
Well, how long will you be gone?
8개월요
Eight months.
- 꽤 오래 가 있네요
- 놀러오면 되잖아요
-That's a really long time.
-Yeah, but you could come and visit.
거기서도 방을 몇 개는
소유할 수 있을 거예요
I bet you could own
a few places down there.
먼저 집부터
사야 할 것 같은데
Oh, you know, I should probably
buy a place in the city first.
아, 무슨 말인지 알았어요
And I just got what you meant.
That is..
- 이번엔 어려웠어요
- 어려웠죠
-That's a tricky one.
-It's tricky.
Good luck.
행운을 빌어요
You too.
저도요
아직 연습 중이란 걸
Now, remember, I'm still learning.
명심해 둬
하나, 둘, 셋, 넷!
One, two, three, four!
You know this song. Sing along.
노래 알면 따라 해
어때?
So?
- 안 돼
No!